

Trinidad and Tobago +18683736774 shenice625@hotmail.com

I am a motivated professional offering 5 years of experience in administrative duties and 3 years of experience in digital marketing, with a history of devising and implementing successful marketing campaigns. I have a deep understanding of target audiences and competitors, enabling me to develop effective marketing campaigns. As an early adopter of the latest trends and strategies, I have brought consistently fresh and creative ideas to the table. I also have experience delivering customer service, including clerical support and public interaction. Additionally, my skillset is rich in calendar management, scheduling, data entry, and database administration. I am confident that I can add value to any organization in need of excellent collaboration, interpersonal, and multitasking abilities, and I am always prepared to meet tight deadlines.

Moreover, I am a proud small ecommerce business owner that was started during the pandemic, which helped fostered a love and passion for marketing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amazon PPC Specialist (Freelance)

03/2023 to 04/2023

Amz

Online

- Created image plans for Amazon sellers and vendors
- Monitored and evaluated sales performance to make informed decisions and improve results.
- Conducted market research and analyzed competitors to identify opportunities and maintain competitive edge.
- Developed and executed marketing campaigns to increase online sales and customer engagement.
- · Managed campaign level budgets & adjusting bids to optimize the ROI
- Uploading A+ Content (Enhanced Brand Content) and to Manage Stores.
- · Creating Weekly and Monthly reports on Google Sheets to share with clients.

Website development and design (Freelance)

04/2023 to 05/2023

Organic Pantry

Trinidad and Tobago

- Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot, and other editing software.
- Ran debugging tools to eliminate flaws and glitches prior to publishing.
- Provided security maintenance and patching on website interface to maintain viability after launch.
- Optimized web applications for speed, scalability and security.
- Crafted SEO strategy and intuitive interface for site to achieve prominent rankings across top browser platforms
- · Completed domain name registrations and maintained website and web hosting account.
- Developed graphic and image assets for both content and digital marketing efforts.
- · Promoted brand identity by creating company logos and delivering attractive, user-friendly and unique website.

Marketing Intern (Remote)

03/2023 to 06/2023

Money Mouth Marketing

New York

- · Helped with planning and hosting of marketing events.
- Assisted in creating written, video and image content for marketing channels.
- Scheduled social media postings to advertise products and generate site traffic.
- · Assisted with development of event strategies and tactical plans to promote accomplishment of marketing goals.
- Contributed to mock-ups, email campaigns, and social media content.
- Wrote copy for social media posts, promotional emails and other marketing collateral.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop and implement market research strategies.
- Managed campaigns for various clients that consistently exceeded sales goals.

Managing Director

02/2020

Urban Imports/ Hair Palacett

Trinidad and Tobago

- · Prepared bank deposits and handled business sales, returns and transaction reports.
- · Consulted with customers to assess needs and propose optimal solutions.
- Put together realistic budgets based upon costs and fees for successfully operating business.
- Developed and implemented marketing strategies to generate new customers and increase sales and profit margins.
- Oversaw business budget planning and administration, accounting functions, purchasing, and bi-weekly payroll to handle financial needs.
- Conducted target market research to discover customer needs and analyze competitor trends.
- Managed purchasing, sales, marketing and customer account operations efficiently.
- Negotiated price and service with customers and vendors to decrease expenses and increase profit.
- Recruited, hired, and trained initial personnel, working to establish key internal functions and outline scope of
 positions for new organization.
- Monitored daily cash discrepancies, inventory shrinkage and drive-off.

Administrative/Customer service Representative

01/2017 to 12/2017

William's Botholomew and Associates Ltd.

Trinidad and Tobago

- · Handled customer inquiries and suggestions courteously and professionally.
- · Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor.
- · Answered constant flow of customer calls with minimal wait times.
- Answered customer telephone calls promptly to avoid on-hold wait times.
- · Coordinated and scheduled meetings and conference calls to optimize scheduling of senior staff.
- Scheduled office meetings and client appointments for staff teams.
- Executed record filing system to improve document organization and management.
- Restocked supplies and placed purchase orders to maintain adequate stock levels.

SKILLS

Website development

Accounting, Bookkeeping, Peachtree

Email & Calendar management

Social media marketing/management

Lead generation & Cold Calling

SEO

Project Management

Branding

Website Analytics tools

https://hairpalacett.com/

https://urbanimportstt.com/

EDUCATION

Udemy

The Complete Digital Marketing Course Online

10/2022 to 02/2023

Synergy Training Institute

Accounts Payable, Accounts Receivable, Peachtree Trinidad and Tobago 09/2023 to 12/2023

Cipriani College of Labour and Co-operative studies

Associate

Communication studies & Occupational Safety and Health Trinidad and Tobago 01/2017 to 12/2019